A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, The Fund for the Advancement of Education (TFAE) files FA740
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant Awardees – Educational Institutions, 1947-1976; II; 92.4 Cubic Feet 77 boxes.
  - General Correspondence Files, 1947-1972; 2; 32.4 Cubic Feet 27 boxes.; 27 boxes.
    - U, 1951-1971
      - United States House of Representatives - Select Committee on Government Research, 1963 (Box 25 (49629))
      - United States Industries, 1963 (Box 25 (49629))
      - United States Military Academy, 1963 (Box 25 (49629))
      - United States Office of Education, 1961-1962 (Box 25 (49629))
      - United States Steel, 1962-1963 (Box 25 (49629))
      - United States Student Aid Funds, Inc., 1961 (Box 25 (49629))
      - Universidad de Valle, Colombia, 1962 (Box 25 (49629))
      - University Center in Virginia, 1961-1963 (Box 25 (49629))
      - University Council for Educational Administration, 1961-1966 (Box 25 (49629))
      - Upstate Medical Center, Syracuse, NY (Bettye Caldwelle), 1965 (Box 25 (49629))
      - Utah, University of, 1961 (Box 25 (49629))
      - Utica College [Confidential], 1961-1963 (Box 25 (49629))
    - V, 1956-1965
      - V - General [4 Folders], 1961-1965 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Vaizey, John, 1960-1963 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Vanderbilt University, 1963 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Vasser College, 1961 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Video Tape Installations, 1956-1959 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Video Tape Productions of New York, Inc., 1961 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Virgin Islands of the United States, 1959-1964 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Visit to U.S., European Educational Television Experts, 1960 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Voluntary Organizations and a World Without War, 1963 (Box 26 (49630))
    - W, 1954-1973
      - W - [18 Folders], 1959-1973 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Wagner College, 1961 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Mary Ward House of Studies, 1964 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Washburn University of Topeka, 1962 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Washington Center for Metropolitan Studies, 1962-1964 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Washington County (Hagerstown, MD), 1961-1966 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Washington High School, George, 1962-1963 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Washington University, George, 1963 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Washington University (St. Louis), 1961-1962 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Washington, University of [2 Folders], 1961-1965 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Waterbury, Lester E., 1963 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Wayne State University, 1961-1966 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Webb, John Crawford, 1963 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Webster College, 1961 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Wellesley College, 1961 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Wellmuth, John J. (Institute of Philosophical Research), 1956 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Wesleyan University - Middletown, 1961-1962 (Box 26 (49630))
      - West Virginia Wesleyan College, 1961 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Western College Association, 1961 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education, 1963 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Western Personnel Institute, 1961-1963 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Westinghouse Electric Cororation, 1959-1964 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Westminster College, 1958-1962 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Westmont College, 1962 (Box 26 (49630))
      - Weston Public Schools (Weston, MA) [2 Folders], 1959-1965 (Box 26 (49630))
      - White, Harvey - Physics Films - Reports, 1957 (Box 26 (49630))
      - White House Conference on Education - Reports, 1955 (Box 27 (49631))
      - Wilberforce University, 1962 (Box 27 (49631))
      - Wilkinson, Bonnie, 1954 (Box 27 (49631))
      - Willard School, Emma, 1962 (Box 27 (49631))
      - Williams College, 1962 (Box 27 (49631))
      - Williams College of Chicago, George, 1963 (Box 27 (49631))
      - Wilson, Craig, 1961-1962 (Box 27 (49631))
      - Winchester Public Schools, 1963 (Box 27 (49631))
      - Winstead, Warren J. (Direcor of Education, U.S. Army), 1961-1964 (Box 27 (49631))
      - Wisconsin State, 1963 (Box 27 (49631))
      - Wisconsin, University of [2 Folders], 1961-1964 (Box 27 (49631))
      - Withers, Samuel, 1963 (Box 27 (49631))
      - Wittcoff, Raymond H. (President, Transurban Investment Corp.), 1962 (Box 27 (49631))
      - Wofford, John G., 1963 (Box 27 (49631))
      - Wolozin, Harold, 1961-1962 (Box 27 (49631))
      - Woodhouse, Chase Going (Service Bureau for Woman's Organizations), 1961 (Box 27 (49631))
      - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation, 1962-1963 (Box 27 (49631))
      - Wooster, College of, 1961 (Box 27 (49631))
      - World Fair - Hall of Education, 1960-1961 (Box 27 (49631))
      - Worm Runners Digest (Informal Journal of Comparative Psychology, Britannica Center, and University of Michigan), 1961 (Box 27 (49631))
      - Wright, Harry M., 1962-1963 (Box 27 (49631))
  - Fund Administered Projects, 1954-1972; 3; 2.4 Cubic Feet 2 boxes.; 2 boxes.
    The Fund Administered Projects sub-series consists of files on projects directed by TFAE and is comprised of grants and meetings summaries. Projects of note in the sub-series include: The Computer in American Education; Improvements in Elementary School Teaching; and Design Models of Alternative Education. Box 2 includes grants and meeting agenda related to the Role of Education in American History.
    - Adejunmobi, Nathaniel (FAP #91) [Photograph], 1967 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Atlanta Meeting of Negro College Students - June 16-17, 1966 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Bernstein, Basil (FAP #46), 1966 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Bloom, Sophie (FAP #46), 1965-1966 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Brandeis Day School (FAP #46), 1966 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Chelsea Closed Circuit TV Report - Mailing, 1963 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Computer in American Education - Book, 1967 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Decade of Experiment - A Ten Year Report, 1961 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Design Models of Alternative Educational Systems for the Future (FAP #88), 1966-1967 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Evaluation and Preparation of Report on Faculty Leave Program (FAP #86), 1966-1967 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Ferrer, Terry - Classroom Revolution - Booklet, 1963 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Follow-Up and Report on Early Admission to College Program (FAP #87), 1965-1967 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Goodlad, John I. - School Curriculum Reform - Book, 1964-1965 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Great Ideas in Antiquity (FAP #63), 1963 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Hudson Public Schools - John P. McDowell (FAP #46), 1966 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Improvements in Elementary School Teaching (FAP #84) - 1966-1967 Correspondence (Box 1 (49632))
    - Improvements in Elementary School Teaching (FAP #84) - 1966 Correspondence (Box 1 (49632))
    - Improvements in Elementary School Teaching (FAP #84) - 1965 Correspondence (Box 1 (49632))
    - Improvements in Elementary School Teaching (FAP #84) - 1964 Correspondence (Box 1 (49632))
    - Library of Congress - Catalog numbers for The Fund for the Advancement of Education publications, 1961-1966 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Longsworth, Charles R. (FAP #46), 1965 (Box 1 (49632))
    - MacBeth, Edwin (FAP #46), 1966 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Maloney, Patricia (FAP #46), 1965 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Mohan, Dr. Bernard (FAP #46), 1966 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Marke, Julius J. - Copyright and Public Domain (FAP #89), 1966-1967 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Permissions (for reprints and quotations of The Fund for the Advancement of Education publications), 1963-1967 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Publications (The Fund for the Advancement of Education) - General data, 1963-1968 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Stock reports, 1963-1967 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Survey of Social Studies Curriculum Projects (FAP #85), 1965-1966 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Writing the History of The Fund for the Advancement of Education - Paul Woodring (FAP #94), 1967-1972 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Writing the History of The Fund for the Advancement of Education - Reports (FAP #94), 1970-1971 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Wu, Nelson I. (FAP #46), 1967 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Young, Michael (FAP #46), 1965 (Box 1 (49632))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36), 1965-1966 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Buck, Paul, 1961-1963 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Buck, Paul, 1958-1959 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - California, University of - Grant, 1959-1962 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Cambridge Meeting - November 28, 1960 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Cambridge Meeting - March 6, 1957 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Cambridge Meeting - July 8, 1956 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Cambridge Meeting - May 12, 1956 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Cambridge Conference - November 15, 1957 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Chicago, University of - Grant, 1958-1959 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Columbia University - Grant, 1958-1960 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Columbia University - Additional grant - Hofstadter and Smith, 1959 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Columbia University - Grant - McLachlan, James S., 1960 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Columbia University - Grant - Ross, Dorothy R., 1961 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Committee Meeting - November 13, 1964 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Committee Meeting - March 6, 1964 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Committee Meeting - April 26, 1963 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Committee Meeting - November 15, 1962 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Committee Meeting - March 30, 1962 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Conference in Hamburg, 1967 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Conference of Historians and Archivists -September 12, 1961 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - East Texas State College - Grant - Chasteen, R.J., 1961 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - East Texas State College - Grant, 1959-1961 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Finance, 1958-1961 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Harvard University - Calhoun, D.H., 1963-1966 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Harvard University - Grant, 1959-1961 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Harvard University - Messerli, Jonathan, 1962 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Indiana University - Grant, 1957-1961 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Johns Hopkins University - Grant, 1960-1961 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Kentucky Research Foundation - Grant, 1958-1962 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Minnesota, University of - Kromer, Edith, 1967-1969 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Minnesota, University of - Supplemental grant - Schmitt, Peter, 1964-1966 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Minnesota, University of - Grant - Barton, Briggs and T. Smith, 1968-1971 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Minnesota, University of - Grant - Schmitt, Peter, 1963 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Minnesota, University of - Grant, 1961 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Minnesota, University of - Immigrants in the United States, 1964 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - North Carolina, University of - Grant, 1961 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Pamphlet publication and distribution, 1956-1957 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Princeton Conference - March 1-2, 1958, 1957-1958 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Reed College, 1965-1966 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Sherry-Netherlands Meeting - December 11-12, 1954 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Sub-Committee Meeting - May 28, 1960 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Symposium on 19th Century America - Chatham, Massachusetts - June 1964 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Symposium on 19th Century America - Chatham, Massachusetts - June 1964 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Symposium on 19th Century America - Chatham, Massachusetts - June 1964 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Washington University - Grant, 1960 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - West Coast Conference - October 14-15, 1961 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - William and Mary, College of - Grant, 1960 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Williamsburg Conference - October 16-17, 1959 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Wisconsin, State Historical Society of - Grant, 1959 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Wisconsin, State Historical Society of - Report, 1958-1959 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in American History (FAP #36) - Wisconsin, University of - Report - Final (September 1, 1958-November 1, 1960), 1962 (Box 2 (49633))
    - Role of Education in World History, 1955-1959 (Box 2 (49633))
  - Grantee Award Authorization Files, 1951-1969; 4; 4.8 Cubic Feet 4 boxes.; Legal size.; 4 boxes.
    The Grantee Award Authorization Files sub-series is comprised of TFAE forms authorizing grant awards to the various institutions. The forms include a concise description of the program funded, and the terms and conditions of the award.
    - Adult Education Association of the U.S.A. (Washington, DC), 1966 (Box 1 (49634))
    - The Academy of Political Science Columbia University, 1967 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Academy for Educational Development Inc., 1966-1968 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Akron, University of, 1957-1963 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Agricultural, Mechanical & Normal College, 1956 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Alabama Agricultural, Mechanical College, 1965-1968 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Alabama Polytechnic Institute, 1959 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Alabama State Department of Education, 1961 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Alabama, University of, 1956-1961 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Alaska Methodist University, 1958-1959 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Alaska, University of, 1968 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Albion College, 1963 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Alfred University (NY), 1965-1968 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Allegheny College, 1953-1954 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Allegheny County Schools (PA), 1963-1966 (Box 1 (49634))
    - American Association of University Women Educational Foundation, 1961-1963 (Box 1 (49634))
    - American Association of Colleges for Teacher Education, 1958-1960 (Box 1 (49634))
    - American Association of Junior Colleges, 1959-1967 (Box 1 (49634))
    - American College in Paris, 1964 (Box 1 (49634))
    - American Council on Education (Common aspects of citizenship U.S. and Canada), 1953-1959 (Box 1 (49634))
    - American Council of Learned Societies, 1961-1963 (Box 1 (49634))
    - American Educational Research Association, 1956 (Box 1 (49634))
    - American Institute of Architects, 1957 (Box 1 (49634))
    - American Institute of Physics, 1957 (Box 1 (49634))
    - American Personnel and Guidance Association, 1959 (Box 1 (49634))
    - American Philosophical Association, 1956-1957 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Amherst College, 1953-1961 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Antioch College, 1956-1958 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Arizona State Department of Public Instruction, 1966 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Arizona, University of, 1959 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Arkansas Agricultural and Mechanical College, 1956 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Arkansas College, 1956 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Arkansas Polytechnic College, 1953-1957 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Arkansas State College, 1956 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Arkansas, University of, 1952-1959 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Aspen Institute for Humanistic Studies, 1960-1964 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Association of American Colleges, 1952-1961 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Association of American Geographers, 1961-1963 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Associated Colleges of Colorado, 1963 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Associated Colleges of Illinois, Inc., 1959-1960 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Associated Colleges of the Midwest, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Association of Higher Education, 1957 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Association for Educational Data Systems, Inc., 1968 (Box 1 (49634))
    - City of Atlanta, Fulton County (Education Commission), 1958-1961 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Atlanta University, 1952 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Auburn School Department (ME), 1959 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Augustana College, 1955 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Austin College, 1953-1959 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Baker University, 1963 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Baldwin School, 1956-1958 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Baltimore City Public Schools, 1959-1961 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Bank Street College of Education, 1953-1956 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Bard College, 1958-1959 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Barnard College, 1952-1956 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Barnard School for Boys, Inc., 1961-1962 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Barrington Consolidated High School District #224, 1962-1965 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Bates College, 1961-1962 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Beloit College, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Bennington College, 1958-1967 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Bennington College - South Supervisory Union, 1962-1963 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Bennett College, 1959 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Berea College, 1953-1961 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Berkshire Country Day School, 1966 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Bloomingdale Neighborhood Conservation Association, Inc., 1965-1967 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Board of Education, MA - Board of Control - Tape Teaching Project, 1960 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Board of Regional Community Colleges, 1960 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Boston University, 1960 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Bowdoin College, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Boys Club of New York, 1954-1956 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Brandeis University, 1955-1956 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Brevard County Board of Education, 1960-1967 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Birarcliff Public Schools, 1956-1958 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Bridgeport Community School District, 1960-1962 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Bridgeport, University of, 1956-1957 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Brigham Young University, 1963 (Box 1 (49634))
    - British Columbia, University of, 1964-1965 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Brockton Public Schools, 1966 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Brooklyn College, 1952-1958 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Brooklyn College of City University of New York, 1967 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Broward County Board of Public Instruction, 1961-1964 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Brown University, 1952-1966 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Bryn Mawr College, 1959 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Bucknell University, 1958-1960 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Buffalo, University of, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Burke Foundation, Frederic, 1956-1959 (Box 1 (49634))
    - California Council on Teacher Education, 1961-1966 (Box 1 (49634))
    - California Department of Education, 1959-1960 (Box 1 (49634))
    - California, University of, 1956-1968 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Cambridge Center for Social Studies, 1966-1968 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Canadian Council for Programmed Learning, 1963 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Carleton College, 1952-1956 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Carmel Unified School District, 1964 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Carnegie Institute of Technology, 1959-1960 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Case Institute of Technology, 1955-1960 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Catholic School Board of the Archdiocese of Louisville, 1958 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Catholic University of Puerto Rico, 1966-1968 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Center for Advanced Study in Behavioral Sciences, 1958-1966 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Center for Applied Linguistics, 1965 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Central California Educational Television, Inc., 1959 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Central Michigan College of Education - Program - Better utilization of teachers, 1952-1966 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Chapman College, 1962 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Chicago, Board of Education of the City of, 1956-1961 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Chicago, University of, 1952-1964 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Cincinnati Public Schools Board of Education, 1957-1958 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Cincinnati, University of, 1964-1965 (Box 1 (49634))
    - City College (NYC), 1954-1956 (Box 1 (49634))
    - City College Fund (NYC), 1966 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Citizens Scholarship Foundation of America, Inc., 1962 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Civic Education Foundation, 1954-1955
    - Claremont College (Graduate School), 1953-1968 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Coker College for Women, 1954 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Colby College, 1953-1956 (Box 1 (49634))
    - College Entrance Examination Board, 1955-1965 (Box 1 (49634))
    - College of William and Mary, 1959 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Colgate University, 1954-1966 (Box 1 (49634))
    - The Collegiate School, 1959-1961 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Colorado State Department of Education, 1957-1966 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Colorado, University of, 1956-1965 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Columbia University, 1953-1968 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Committee on Assessing the Progress of Education, 1966-1968 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Committee for Economic Development, 1953 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Community consolidated High School District #234 (Chicago, IL), 1960
    - Connecticut College, 1954-1955 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Concord Public Schools, 1966-1967 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Connecticut State Board of Education, 1957-1959 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Connecticut, University of, 1956-1957 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Connecticut Citizens for the Public Schools, 1958 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Cooperative Program for Preparation of Teachers, 1955 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Cornell College, 1953-1954 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Cornell University, 1953-1958 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Corning City School District, 1959 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Council for the Advancement of Small Colleges, 1958-1963 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Council for Financial Aid to Education, 1954-1962 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Council of Higher Educational Institutions in New York City, 1962 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Council for Indepenent School Aid, Inc., 1964
    - Council for the Study of Mankind, 1964 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Cultural Educational Tour Institute, 1966-1968 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Dade County Board of Education, 1957-1964 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Dalhousie University, 1966 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Darien Public Schools, 1964 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Dartmouth College, 1953-1955 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Davidson College, 1952-1961 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Dearborn Public Schools, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Denison University, 1952-1953 (Box 1 (49634))
    - De Pauw University, 1953-1960 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Detroit Board of Education, 1957-1961 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Detroit, University of, 1957 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Dillard University, 1953-1963 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Drake University, 1953-1954 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Drew University, 1968 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Duke University, 1956-1959 (Box 1 (49634))
    - Dunwoody Industrial Institute, William Hood, 1966 (Box 1 (49634))